Guide to the Emilie F. Miller papers, 1987-1991
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
  - Senate Bill 660- Recycling 1, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Senate Bill 660- Recycling 2, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Senate Bill 444 Bussing, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - School Counselors, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Senate Bill 502-Bottle Bill, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Share the Ride Correspondence, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Highway Funds, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - United Airlines Facility, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1992 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1993 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Affordable Housing Letters, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Anita B. Glover- Virginia Department of Taxation, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Boards and Commissions Recommendations 1, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Boards and Commissions Recommendations 2, 1990-1991 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Boards and Commissions Recommendations 3, 1989-1990 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Boards and Commissions Recommendations 4, 1988-1991 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Brain Dion- "Gift Lot" Subdivision, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Mrs. Cary, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Scott A. Christofferson, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Clean Indoor Act, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Columbia Pines Citizens Association Road Maintenance, 1977-1988 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Constituent Call Forms, 1980s-1990s (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Cornelius A. Dolby- Move of Virginia Employment Commission, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Constituent File Forms/Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - House Bill 117- Dental Hygienists Letters, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Hate Mail to Senator Miller, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Downzoning Letters 1, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Downsizing Letters 2, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Downsizing Letters 3, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Downsizing Letters 4, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Drug and Alcohol, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Roads- Repair of Patches, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Emil Franks Clozaril Coverage by Medicaid, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Fairfax Villa- Street Repair, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - John Paul Forest II, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence to January 31, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, February 1990 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, March 1990 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, April 1990 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence, May 1990 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence, June 1990 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence, July 1990 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, August 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, September 1990 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, October 1990 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, November 1990 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, December 1990 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, January 1991 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, February 1991 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, March 1991 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, April 1991 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, May 1991 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, June 1991 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, July 1991 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, August 1991 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, September 1991 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, October 1991 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, November 1991 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Goodwin House, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Greenway Downs Subdivision Virginia Department of Transportation Problem, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - House Bill 721, 1990-1991 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Holmes Run Village, 1989-1990 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Jane Woods, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Lakeside Plaza Condominium, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Letters to be Written (Congratulations), 1991 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Mantua Elementary School 1991 Richmond Visit (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Maynard Hamilton- World War II 50th Anniversary, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Miriam Wimberly- Blue Cross/Blue Shield, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Montessori Schools and House Bill 1035, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Skyline Plaza Condominium, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - State Corporation and Virginia Power- Energy Efficiency Concerns, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Uniform Certification of Engineers Letters, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Walnut Hills- Sidewalks, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Willow Springs Civic Association, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Yorktowne Square Condominiums 1, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Yorktowne Square Condominiums 2, 1986-1991 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Senate Bill 821- Admission of Qualified Students, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Senate Bill 477- Admission of Qualified Students to Public Institutions of Higher Education, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Alumni Letters, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Military Institute Alumni Suit, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Military Institute Article (Lex Claudia), December 15, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Bill Budget Amendment, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Military Institute- BPW- Resolution, circa 1990 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Military Institute Correspondence 1, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Military Institute Correspondence 2, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Military Institute Correspondence 3, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Military Institute Correspondence 4, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Military Institute Correspondence, June 1991 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Military Institute Correspondence 1, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Military Institute Correspondence 2, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Military Institute Crossfire, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Dick's Response to "VMI People", 1991 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Governor Wilder Press Release, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Military Institute Information, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Military Institute Information (Campaign), 1991 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Legal Defense Funds for Virginia Military Institute Bill, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Legal References 1, 1988-1991 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Legal References 2, 1988-1991 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Military Institute Letters, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Letter to Governor Baliles- Virginia Military Institute, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Lex Claudia, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Lex Claudia, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Lex Claudia Article, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Lex Claudia- Edited Virginia Military Institute Article 1, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Lex Claudia- Edited Virginia Military Institute Article 2, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Military Institute Opinion- United States of America v. Commonwealth of Virginia 1, June 17, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Military Institute Opinion- United States of America v. Commonwealth of Virginia 2, June 17, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Military Institute Poll Data, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Pornographic and Anonymous Letters, circa 1990 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Press, 1990s (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Press, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Press 1, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Press 2, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Press 3, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Conferences, 1990s (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Press Atlanta Constitution Article, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Military Institute Press Clippings, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Military Institute Press- Miller Cited or Quoted 1, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Military Institute Press- Miller Cited or Quoted 2, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Military Institute Press- Miller Cited or Quoted 3, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Military Institute Press, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Military Institute Press Information, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Press Release, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Military Institute Speech, April 1989 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Military Institute- TAG, Lottery, 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Military Institute Trial- Press 1, 1985-1995 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Military Institute Trial- Press 2, 1985-1995 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Military Institute Trial- Press 3, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - United States of America vs. Commonwealth of Virginia and Virginia Military Institute- Alumni Counterclaim, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Military Institute vs. United States of America- Thornburgh, 1990s (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Military Institute- Women Attorneys Association, 1989-1996 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Working for Sex Equity in Insurance Information and Strategy Packet 1, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Working for Sex Equity in Insurance Information and Strategy Packet 2, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Working for Sex Equity in Insurance Information and Strategy Packet 3, 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Working for Sex Equity in Insurance Information and Strategy Packet 4, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - American Association on Mental Retardation (AAMR), 1991 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Fairfax County Council of the Arts Calendar, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Virginia High School League Calendar for 1990-1991 School Year (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - "Cardiac Arrest" 1, April 25, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives, Washington, D.C., December 14-16 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives, December 101-11, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - National Organization of Women Legislators Conference- Mackinac Island, Michigan, August 23-27, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence 1, April 1990 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Conference-Renee Ross Naples, Florida, March 7-9, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - VACSB Conference, Richmond, Virginia, January 22-24, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - National Womens Political Caucus Convention, July 11-12, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Commission on Population Growth and Development- Wintergreen, Virginia, November 21-22, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence 2, April 1990 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - 1991 Democratic Leadership Council- Cleveland, Ohio, May 5-7, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Department of Health and Human Services Workshop, July 22-26, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Fairfax City Community Calendar, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Global Leaders for the South Leadership Forum, May 19-24,1991 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Hawall's Healthy Start- Honolulu, Hawaii, February 5-7, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Labor Issues 1992: Rebuilding America- San Diego, California, November 22-23, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - SBA Legislative Conference- Kansas City, November 17-20, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Letters, 1977-1982 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Fall Dates, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures, April 11-13, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures State-Federal Meeting, May 2-4, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Photocopies of Blank Senate Schedules, 1980s-1990s (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Russell, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Schedule Book, January 1991 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Schedule Book, February 1991 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Schedule Book, March 1991 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Schedule Book, September 1991 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Schedule Book, October 1991 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Schedule Book, November 1991 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Schedule Book, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Schedule Information, December 23-29, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Schedule Information, December 30, 1990 -January 5, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Schedule Information, January 6-January 12, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Schedule Information, January 13-19, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Scheduled Event, January 20-26, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Scheduled Event, January 27-February 2, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Scheduled Event, February 4-10, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Scheduled Event, February 11-17, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Scheduled Event, February 18-24, 991 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Scheduled Event, February 25-March 3, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Schedule Information, March 4-10, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Scheduled Event, March 11-17, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Scheduled Event, March 18-24, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Scheduled Event, March 25-31, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Scheduled Event, April 1-8, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Scheduled Event, April 9-15, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Scheduled Event, April 16-22, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Scheduled Event, April 23-28, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Scheduled Event, April 29-May 5, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Scheduled Event, May 13-20, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Scheduled Event, May 21-28, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Scheduled Event, May 28-June 2, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Scheduled Event, June 3-9, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Scheduled Event, June 10-16, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Scheduled Event, June 17-23, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Scheduled Event, June 24-30, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Scheduled Event, July 4, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Scheduled Event, July 1-7, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Scheduled Event, July 8-14, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Scheduled Event, July 22-28, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Scheduled Event, July 15-21, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Scheduled Event, July 29-August 4, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Scheduled Event, August 5-11, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Scheduled Event, August 12-18, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Scheduled Event, August 19-25, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Scheduled Event, August 26-September 1, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Scheduled Event, September 2-8, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Scheduled Event, September 9-15, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Scheduled Event, September 16-22, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Scheduled Event 1, September 23-29, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Scheduled Event 2, September 23-29, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Scheduled Event, September 30-October 6, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Scheduled Event, October 7-10, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Scheduled Event, October 11-13, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Scheduled Event, October 14-20, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Scheduled Event, October 21-27, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Scheduled Event, October 28-November 3, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Scheduled Event, November 4-10, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Scheduled Event, November 11-17, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Scheduled Event, November 18-19, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Scheduled Event, November 17-24, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Scheduled Event, November 25-December 1, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Scheduled Event, December 2-8, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Scheduled Event, December 9-31, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - 1991 Schedule of Events- Women's National Democratic Club (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Schedule- Pending, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Southern Legislative Conference- New Orleans, Louisiana, July 20-24, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Southern Legislative Conference- Pinehurst, North Carolina, November 10-13, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures- Federal Assembly Orlando, Florida, August 11-15, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Federal Assembly Washington, D.C., December 11-13, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Southeast United States/Korea Economic Council- Charleston, South Carolina, November 18-20, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Women in Government- Scottsdale, Arizona, January 2-5, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - 1991 Congressional Redistricting 1 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - 1991 Congressional Redistricting 2 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 11/House Joint Resolution 41- Maternal and Perinatal Drug Exposure and Abuse 1, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 11/House Joint Resolution 41- Maternal and Perinatal Drug Exposure and Abuse 2, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 11/House Joint Resolution 41- Maternal and Perinatal Drug Exposure and Abuse 3, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 11/House Joint Resolution 41- Maternal and Perinatal Drug Exposure and Abuse 4, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 11/House Joint Resolution 41- Maternal and Perinatal Drug Exposure and Abuse 5, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 11/House Joint Resolution 41- Maternal and Perinatal Drug Exposure and Abuse 6, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 11/House Joint Resolution 41- Maternal and Perinatal Drug Exposure and Abuse 7, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 11/House Joint Resolution 41- Maternal and Perinatal Drug Exposure and Abuse 7, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 11/House Joint Resolution 41- Maternal and Perinatal Drug Exposure and Abuse 8, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 11/House Joint Resolution 41- Maternal and Perinatal Drug Exposure and Abuse 9, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 11/House Joint Resolution 41- Maternal and Perinatal Drug Exposure and Abuse 10, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 11/House Joint Resolution 41- Maternal and Perinatal Drug Exposure and Abuse 11, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 11/House Joint Resolution 41- Maternal and Perinatal Drug Exposure and Abuse 12, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Daycare Study 1, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Daycare Study 2, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Daycare Study 3, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Daycare Study 4, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - House Joint Resolution 124-Early Childhood Education and Daycare Study 1, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - House Joint Resolution 124-Early Childhood Education and Daycare Study 2, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - House Joint Resolution 124-Early Childhood Education and Daycare Study 3, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - House Joint Resolution 124-Early Childhood Education and Daycare Study 4, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - House Joint Resolution 124-Early Childhood Education and Daycare Study 5, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - House Joint Resolution 124-Early Childhood Education and Daycare Study 6, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - House Joint Resolution 124-Early Childhood Education and Daycare Study 7, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - House Joint Resolution 124-Early Childhood Education and Daycare Study 8, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - House Joint Resolution 164- Intervention Services to Handicapped Infants and Toddlers 1, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - House Joint Resolution 164- Intervention Services to Handicapped Infants and Toddlers 2, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - House Joint Resolution 164- Intervention Services to Handicapped Infants and Toddlers 3, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - House Joint Resolution 164- Intervention Services to Handicapped Infants and Toddlers 4, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - House Joint Resolution 164- Intervention Services to Handicapped Infants and Toddlers 5, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - House Joint Resolution 164- Intervention Services to Handicapped Infants and Toddlers 6, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - House Joint Resolution 164- Intervention Services to Handicapped Infants and Toddlers 7, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - House Joint Resolution 164- Intervention Services to Handicapped Infants and Toddlers 8, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Early Intervention Study Committee 1, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Early Intervention Study Committee 2, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Early Intervention Study Committee 3, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Early Intervention Study Committee 4, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Early Intervention Study Committee 5, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Early Intervention Study Committee 6, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Early Intervention Study Committee 7, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Early Intervention Study Committee 8, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Education and Health Committee 1, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Education and Health Committee 2, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Education and Health Committee 3, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Education and Health Committee 4, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Education and Health Committee 5, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Education and Health Higher Education Subcommittee, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Freedom of Information Act Joint Subcommittee Study- Inactive File 1, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Freedom of Information Act Joint Subcommittee Study- Inactive File 2, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Freedom of Information Act Joint Subcommittee Study- Inactive File 3, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Freedom of Information Act Joint Subcommittee Study- Inactive File 4, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Freedom of Information Act Joint Subcommittee 1, 1989-1991 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Freedom of Information Act Joint Subcommittee 2, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Freedom of Information Act Joint Subcommittee 3, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Freedom of Information Act Joint Subcommittee 4, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - General Laws Committee-1, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - General Laws Committee- 2, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Guardianship, Joint Subcommittee Study, 1988-1989 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Local Government Committee 1, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Local Government Committee 2, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Local Government Committee 3, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Local Government Committee 4, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Local Government Committee -TDR's Study 1, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Local Government Committee-TDR's Study 2, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Local Government Committee-TDR's Study 3, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Local Government Committee-TDR's Study 4, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Local Government Committee -TDR's Study 5, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Local Government Committee -TDR's Study 6, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Local Government Committee -TDR's Study 7, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Local Government Committee -TDR's Study 8, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Local Government Committee -TDR's Study 9, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Local Government Committee -TDR's Study 10, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Task Force on Developmental Disabilities 1, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Task Force on Developmental Disabilities 2, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Task Force on Developmental Disabilities 3, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Task Force on Developmental Disabilities 4, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Task Force on Developmental Disabilities 5, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Task Force on Developmental Disabilities 6, 1990s (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Task Force on Developmental Disabilities 7, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Task Force on Developmental Disabilities 8, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Task Force on Developmental Disabilities 9, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Task Force on Developmental Disabilities 10, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Task Force on Developmental Disabilities 11, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 7)